You win!
Here we are,
traveling through the forest to
defeat the Stratum Lord and hopefully
turn the trees that used to be
villagers back into people again.
My goodness, this is all quite a bother.
I shall absorb the
felled tree with fields.
The monsters aren't attacking
the village anymore,
But felling trees is
sending them into a frenzy.
Barrier!
And launch reinforced plastic
bottles filled with pachinko balls!
Oh gross!
Why's it gotta be so stinky?
They smell bad, they taste great!
Don't eat too much now or
you'll be too full to fight.
The Elder Tree Fiend
Stratum Lord it's still not
coming after us it was
originally quite gentle.
Sort of guardian deity
for this stratum when
it attacked the village
we were all shocked.
I for one blame the Nether
Lord that may be but
if you want to turn the
tree people back to normal?
well, then we'll have to beat it.
Indeed,
and I'm positive that
pouring this anti-plant
poison right onto it
should accomplish that.
The plan is to use Lamas,
Kuroyata, and the old man's magic
to pour what's in those barrels?
into its eyes and mouth.
To do that, we'll have to get to its
base first, which is no easy task.
And who knows how much time we have.
On the outside I'm just a big metal box
but inside I've still got a human soul.
In this new world of
wonders I travel to and
fro on the back of my
super strong partner.
Llamas the name's Boxo hello
there that means yes by the way.
I'll
see you
next
time.
Voxo, all my energy is depleted
because I'm so hungry I can't move.
Yeah, yeah, save me here.
It's absolutely freezing out here.
It sucks that we can't even
start a fire to warm up.
Not to rub it in, but I don't feel cold.
Not with this awesome magic
cloak I got from Voxo.
Yes, the cloak from the weapons shop.
I bought it and gave
it to Lamas as a gift.
Didn't you get me anything, Boxo?
I look forward to serving you again.
Wow, way to dodge the question.
How about you revisit this
love triangle drama later, huh?
I'm so hungry my stomach's turned into
some kind of monster eating itself.
I think I'm next.
Oh, right.
I mustn't forget my duty
as a vending machine.
It's cold, so how about some cup ramen?
No, let's make dinner a
little more elaborate.
Form change!
Boxo changed into a shape
I've never seen before.
Are these new products?
Hello there!
Quick question, folks.
Have you ever heard of
the term auto restaurant?
They were 24-hour vending machine-only
restaurants that were once built
along highways where motorists could
pull over and eat anytime they wanted.
They were a big fad, and they coincided
with the spreading craze of video games.
But about 10 years later, with the
advent of the convenience store,
their numbers started
to gradually decline.
Check it out!
This is one of those retro-bending
machines that once took the world by storm.
Oh, this is different
from the usual pasta.
It's kind of thick.
And it's so warm and savory!
The thick pasta is more filling,
and this broth is to die for!
What an unusual flavor!
Boxo, how do you always deliver?
Kelp broth is rare in this world.
People go wild for it.
I want some! Yeah, me too!
Give me three!
Give me four!
And I want second!
I can't stop there, though, no way!
Nah, we're changing the menu.
Form change!
Huh, he turned into a
different shape already?
Now do we get to try the
food in this picture?
It's brooming with meat juice!
This is a new favorite!
Sweet!
Looks like this went over well, too!
Boxo, I think this is the best
thing you've given us yet!
Hot and fresh and tasty!
I'll say, delicious meat surrounded
by two pieces of bread, genius.
In my former life as a vending
machine enthusiast, this was my hobby.
I loved traveling from
place to place sampling
all the different vending
machine's products.
My friends judged my hobby, calling
it a waste of time and money.
But I sure am happy that it's proving
useful to the people of this world.
Kiko, you and I are taking
turns being in charge of meals.
We can't use fire,
so all she can fix are fruits and
vegetables that can be eaten raw.
Those are a big hit, though.
So good, can't handle it!
And there's plenty more
where that came from!
More, please!
I might be getting annoyed.
Some decades back, someone defeated
one of the Elder Tree Fiends.
I hear they did it by burning
it to a crisp with fire magic.
That started a great fire on this stratum.
And for ten years it was a sad place where
neither monsters nor people could live.
Oh, so that must be why fire
is banned in this forest.
I gotta say, it's kind of inconvenient
not being able to use fire.
That it is.
It's surprisingly chilly
at night in the forest.
All the more so after all the
sweaty work during the day.
And everyone's covered in dirt.
If only they could take a nice hot bath.
Wait a minute!
I almost forgot about my hot
springs vending machine function.
Great!
Here comes the next one! Ready.
First, the foundation.
Above that goes the bathtub, and
over there's the changing area.
This is definitely a high-level
collaborative DIY project.
The handcrafted open-air bath is complete.
So quick!
Hot water time!
Looking good so far.
Pulumi's design was flawless as usual.
Oh, my. This is impressive.
There is, however, no guarantee
that no monsters lurk nearby.
As such, I volunteer for guard duty.
Fear not.
I swear by the gods that I would
never even dream of peeping.
You needn't bother.
But thanks.
Botan and Kurayatsu
will stand guard for us.
First bath in a while.
Oh, man, I can hardly wait.
Wait, what's Boxo doing here?
Hello there.
Well, we are gonna need towels and
that foamy liquid stuff after all.
Yes, but we can get those in advance.
There's no reason to wait.
Have you forgotten?
Inside of Boxo, there lives the soul
of a human man with all its foibles.
Yeah, that may be true, but as long
as it's just Boxo, I don't mind.
Why are you two just
standing there gabbing?
You forget that there are
monsters in this forest?
You gotta get in, get
out, and nobody gets hurt.
Well, I'm with Lamas.
I mean, I suppose I don't really mind
either, as long as it's only Voxo.
Lom, it's...
Yeah, Voxo?
Over there.
Sorry, Voxo. Hello there.
I'll go ahead and buy enough for everyone.
Let's see, we'll need more towels
and some of that foamy stuff.
I guess you and I are both standing guard.
Hmm?
This must be what paradise is like. Wow.
I honestly can't believe
how relaxing this is.
I guarantee I'm going
to sleep well tonight.
Warm and cozy.
Kuroyata, what's the matter?
Doesn't the sky over
there seem unusually red?
It can't be.
Oh, no!
The forest is on fire!
Tell everyone to gather up!
No, no...
Black Black, what's going on here?
I don't know what's up
any better than you,
but my guess is that somebody's
burned the elder tree fiends
Stratum Lord to death We can
look into that later right now.
We're racing against time to get out of
this forest You're right, band of gluttons.
If the Stratum Lord has
truly been defeated,
the inhabitants who turned into
trees should have recovered too.
You four go back to the
village and tell them
to evacuate the Clear
Flow Lake Stratum at once.
The transfer circle should be functional.
So what do we do, then?
Some reconnaissance is in order.
We have to confirm that the Elder
Tree Fiend has truly been defeated.
If it hasn't, the people who turned into
trees will burn to death in the Inferno.
We can't have that.
Either uproot or cut down
the surrounding trees.
Kikuyu, go and dispose
of every last plank.
Shui, keep an eye on our
surroundings just in case.
Let's slow that fire
down as much as we can.
Yes, sir!
But will that be enough to
hold back a fire that intense?
I guess it's the only way to survive.
Boxxo, I need a favor. Huh?
Hulemy, do you have some secret plan?
Boxxo, can't you change into something
that dispenses highly flammable oil?
Hello there.
Change into that,
and then I want you to spread oil
from here right to the other side.
What?
Spread kerosene around when
there's a blaze coming?
No way!
That would be like signing
our own death warrants.
I know what I'm doing here.
Please, Boxxo, just trust me.
She means it.
Hello there.
I so appreciate you, Boxxo.
Good. Just like that.
Ah, now I get it.
Fight fire with fire. Voxo?
No.
What are you thinking?
There is a...
Everyone, listen up.
This forest's trees catch fire easily
and then burn up rather quickly.
So if we burn these away first,
we can keep that blaze from
getting any closer to us.
That's an excellent plan.
Sorry, I should have
trusted you. Don't be.
It's still a huge gamble.
This fire's too intense at this rate.
I'll just have to protect
us with my barrier.
But its range is so limited.
To protect this many people.
I don't have time to mull it over.
Boxo?
You're getting massive, so move.
You mean move away from you? Hello there.
Form change!
Oh, close.
Activate barrier!
That's some serious heat.
I'm losing points like crazy.
Things are still a little hot,
but I think we're okay now.
You saved us there, Boxo. You are what?
Oh, um, point. It's low.
Okay.
Thanks for doing that for us.
I hope you know we're grateful.
If we get back safely, I'll
repay you with lots of coins.
Yeah, sorry, Boxo.
When we get home, I'll smash my
piggy bank and help out, too.
The thought alone more than counts.
Thanks, Boxer.
I only have one gold coin on me right
now, but hopefully that will help a bit.
Hello there.
I'll pay up, too.
Don't worry, I'll thank you
properly when we get back.
I'd never live it down
if you thought the Dark
Forest Stratum was full
of chintzy cheapskates.
I may look like a shadow,
but I ain't shady.
Okay, with that settled, I
can be of a bit more use.
If the Elder Tree Fiend has been
defeated, that solves one problem.
But this damage is too extensive.
What damn fool would
have done such a thing?
They'll pay for it when I find them.
I'll put my foot so far up their
ass, they'll taste my shoe leather!
It just has to be dead.
It might just be the bark that's burned.
Don't let your guard down.
There isn't any voice, it would
seem that it is dead indeed.
Llamas, try hitting the trunk at
full strength just to make sure!
Okay, here we go!
Well, that answers that, good Down there,
who dares wake me up from my sweet,
sweet nap?
I believe she is wearing
boots, but they're see-through,
so I don't imagine those can come off.
And just who might you be?
That's rich coming from
you rude intruders.
I'm Kyle Lings, known far and wide
as the terrifying, titillating,
unignorable, shouting, songstress!
Heard of her?
Not even a whisper.
Where are you hick bumpkins from
if you don't even know who I am?
What do you mean where?
D-d-dungeon.
Ah, just forget it!
I don't have time for Lammis idiots!
What, do you guys live
under a rock or something?
Yes, well, our being Lammis idiots aside,
we'd like to know what you're doing here.
You dare ask me?
Fine, I guess I'll tell ya.
To turn this stratum
into a sea of fire And
to kill off every last
lame ass idiot in it,
along with all the stupid
lame ass idiot fools who
are bothering the wicked
metal as hell left on General!
Oh, okay.
So you're working for the Netherlord then.
Yeah! You know it.
I'm one of the Netherlord's
hardcore badass devoted followers.
Call me Kyolings Junior General!
She's probably some sort of undead,
so regular weapons won't work on her.
Attack with caution.
I thought we were gonna trade
some more insults, but fine.
I have no problem with
fighting it out instead.
So go on, attack me, why don't ya?
You think arrows will work?
Do we?
That really hurts!
Of course, those arrows
were endowed with magic.
Magic even works on someone
who's basically a ghost?
My oh my, I don't deal
well with noisy women.
You assholes!
Nobody who wants to live
messes with my head!
What's with you guys?
Didn't expect you to fight like this.
Don't tell me.
You're the ones the Left-Armed
General said to watch out for!
Uh-oh, it looks like Kuro Yadda
went and stole the show, get it?
I didn't do a single thing.
At least we've managed to capture
someone high up that's major.
I just hope we can get some
information out of her.
Hmm.
This definitely wasn't
because our opponent was weak.
This group is
ridiculously strong,
especially those two old folks.
They kicked some butt.
Welp, I didn't manage to do anything,
but I can at least be a good
vending machine and provide enough
food and drink to fill everyone's
bellies after a job well done.
I worked up an appetite.
Loxo, what are you
serving?
As for me, I could use a drink.
Yeah, something nice and refreshing.
Poor Stratum, it sat empty for
decades before and now it will again.
I know telling you not to be
discouraged Might be asking quite a lot,
but we'll accept all the residents?
at Clear Flow Lake Straton.
Of that, you can rest assured.
But did everyone manage
to evacuate in time?
Don't worry, Lamas.
I have faith that the
band of glutton's little
legs reached the village
before the fire did.
And their sense of smell?
It's keen enough to help guide every
last one of the people to safety.
Yeah, I'm sure that you're right.
But still, there was so
much green in this forest.
And now look at it.
I'm not Director Dark,
and it's not my stratum but it does
hurt to see it was so beautiful
before we only did what needed
to be done so there's no use
wringing our hands over it that's
right we tried our very best and
we saved many people that's all
we can do it's enough that we're
all alive and kicking life will
find a way in the forest will be
green again yes the people can
walk on so long as they have the
proper footwear the road may be
rough but a good pair of boots
can carry you far i know heavy's
He's trying to sound encouraging,
but it always gets a little weird the
moment he starts talking about footwear.
Yes, you're right.
We mustn't ever give up, no matter what.
As long as passion fills our
hearts, nothing can stop us.
Everyone's so brave!
Yeah, it's true!
Thanks for cheering me up, guys!
Now, Botan, would you mind
running a little faster?
Welcome back, Director.
I'm glad everyone made it back safely.
Are all in good health? Yes, sir.
The monsters have calmed down
and reconstruction is going well.
Also, yesterday,
a large group of new residents
arrived from the Dark Forest Stratum.
Good work, everyone.
First thing go get some rest
Don't have to tell me twice.
Well, what should we do then?
Just go home and take it easy things
have been hectic So we could do that
Boxxo, what do you want to do?
I want to work
I doubt anyone will have
a problem with that.
I always feel calmer in this stratum
now Let's do some big-time business.
Hello there.
Hmm fresh vegetables.
You bet I'll take some you got any fruit
Everyone, please form a line.
I've prepared lots of vegetables,
so please line up single file.
That way I can distribute
them more quickly.
I was about to run out of ingredients.
Could I get 30 each of those
gourds I got from you before?
Oh, yeah.
I remember, Kiko, you talking about this.
She said that she could do lots of
business selling vegetables on the stratum.
Aha!
So that's where all my
usual customers have gone.
The thief.
This is an even bigger problem
than that chain restaurant debacle.
Hello there. Hello there.
Hello there.
Oh, hey, box of old pal.
Well, glad you're back.
Whoa!
What's all this?
I've never seen these products before.
Bears will eat.
Even in another world, the way to
the ladies' hearts is through sweets.
What will they choose, cake or candy?
It could go either way,
because what I got is tops.
The following day, much to my chagrin,
all the ladies were back in Kikuyu's line.
Hello!
Please form an orderly line.
There are plenty of sugary, hot,
still-baked sweet for babies to go around!
It's autumn now, so selling
sweet potatoes was a good idea.
Too good.
Well, my new rival may have won
this battle, but this is war!
God bless you.
You could even win a reward!
I look forward to serving you again!